Correspondence from the Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Foundation Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1894-1953 (Box 1-109)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1924 (Box-folder 53/7)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1925 (Box-folder 53/8)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 53/9)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1928-1932 (Box-folder 53/10)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1933 (Box-folder 53/11)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 53/12)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 53/13)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1938 (Box-folder 53/14)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1939, 1950 (Box-folder 53/15)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, undated (Box-folder 53/16)
  - Library of Congress. Rogers, Mary R., 1933-1936 (Box-folder 53/17)
  - Library of Congress. Rogers, Mary R., 1937-1939 (Box-folder 53/18)
  - Library of Congress. Rogers, Mary R., 1940-1951 (Box-folder 53/19)
  - Library of Congress. Rogers, Mary R., undated (Box-folder 53/20)
  - Library of Congress. Rogers, Mary R.: carbons of letters (Box-folder 53/21)
  - Library of Congress. Shea, Aileen, 1927-1929 (Box-folder 56/1)
  - Library of Congress. Shea, Aileen, 1930 (Box-folder 56/2)
  - Library of Congress. Shea, Aileen, 1931-1937 (Box-folder 56/3)
  - Library of Congress. Shea, Aileen, carbons of material (Box-folder 56/4)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1937 (Box-folder 57/1)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1938 January-June (Box-folder 57/2)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1938 July-December (Box-folder 57/3)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1939 January-May (Box-folder 57/4)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1939 June-August (Box-folder 57/5)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1939 September-October (Box-folder 57/6)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1939 November-December and miscellaneous 1939 (Box-folder 57/7)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1939 carbons of letters (Box-folder 57/8)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1940 January-February (Box-folder 57/9)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1940 March-May (Box-folder 57/10)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1940 June-December (Box-folder 57/11)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1941 January-March (Box-folder 57/12)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1941 April-June (Box-folder 57/13)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1941 July-September (Box-folder 57/14)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1941 October-December and miscellaneous 1941 (Box-folder 57/15)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1942 January-April (Box-folder 57/16)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1942 May-September (Box-folder 57/17)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1942 October-December and miscellaneous 1942 (Box-folder 57/18)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1943 January-June (Box-folder 58/1)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1943 July-December (Box-folder 58/2)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1944 (Box-folder 58/3)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1945 January-April (Box-folder 58/4)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1945 May-June carbons of letters (Box-folder 58/5)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1945 May-July (Box-folder 58/6)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1945 carbons (Box-folder 58/7)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1945 August-December and miscellaneous 1945 (Box-folder 58/8)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1946 January-June (Box-folder 58/9)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1946 July-September (Box-folder 58/10)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1946 carbons of letters (Box-folder 58/11)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1946 October-December (Box-folder 58/12)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1947 January-April (Box-folder 58/13)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1947 May-June (Box-folder 58/14)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1947 July-September (Box-folder 58/15)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1947 October-December (Box-folder 58/16)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1947 carbons of letters (Box-folder 58/17)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1948 January-March (Box-folder 58/18)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1948 April-June (Box-folder 58/19)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1948 July-September (Box-folder 58/20)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1948 October-December (Box-folder 58/21)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1948 carbons of letters (Box-folder 58/22)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1949 January-April (Box-folder 59/1)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1949 May-June (Box-folder 59/2)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1949 July-October (Box-folder 59/3)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1949 November-December (Box-folder 59/4)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1949 carbons (Box-folder 59/5)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1950 January-February (Box-folder 59/6)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1950 March-June (Box-folder 59/7)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1950 carbons (Box-folder 59/8)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1950 July-December (Box-folder 59/9)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1951 January-April (Box-folder 59/10)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1951 May-August (Box-folder 59/11)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1951 September-December (Box-folder 59/12)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1951 carbons (Box-folder 59/13)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1952 January-April (Box-folder 59/14)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1952 May-June (Box-folder 59/15)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1952 July-December (Box-folder 59/16)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1952 carbons (Box-folder 59/17)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1953 January-June (Box-folder 59/18)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1953 July-1954 February (Box-folder 59/19)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, undated (Box-folder 59/20)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1953 carbons (Box-folder 59/21)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, undated and miscellany (Box-folder 59/22)
  - Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold, 1953-1954, Includes condolence letters regarding Elizabeth S. Coolidge's death. (Box-folder 59/23)
  - Library of Congress. Strunk, Oliver, 1934 (Box-folder 60/1)
  - Library of Congress. Strunk, Oliver, 1935 (Box-folder 60/2)
  - Library of Congress. Strunk, Oliver, 1936 January-March (Box-folder 60/3)
  - Library of Congress. Strunk, Oliver, 1936 April-June (Box-folder 60/4)
  - Library of Congress. Strunk, Oliver, 1936 July-December (Box-folder 60/5)
  - Library of Congress. Strunk, Oliver, 1937 (Box-folder 60/6)
  - Library of Congress. Strunk, Oliver, 1938 (Box-folder 60/7)
  - Library of Congress. Strunk, Oliver, undated (Box-folder 60/8)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1938-1940 (Box-folder 56/5)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1941 (Box-folder 56/6)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1942 (Box-folder 56/7)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1943-1945 (Box-folder 56/8)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1946 (Box-folder 56/9)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1947 (Box-folder 56/10)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1948-1949 (Box-folder 56/11)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1950 (Box-folder 56/12)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1951 (Box-folder 56/13)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1952 (Box-folder 56/14)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., 1953 (Box-folder 56/15)
  - Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N., carbons of letters (Box-folder 56/16)
  - Library of Congress. Gift acknowledgements, 1924-1933 (Box-folder 56/17)
  - Library of Congress. Gift acknowledgements, 1934-1937 (Box-folder 56/18)
  - Library of Congress. Gift acknowledgements, 1938-1953 (Box-folder 56/19)
  - Library of Congress. Round robins (Box-folder 56/20)
  - Library of Congress. Miscellany, 1927-1933 (Box-folder 56/21)
  - Library of Congress. Miscellany, 1935-1953 (Box-folder 56/22)
  - "Lid" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 61/1)
  - Liège, Belgium (Box-folder 61/2)
  - Liège. Concours International d'Œuvres pour Quatuor à cordes (Box-folder 61/3)
  - Liepmann, Klaus see Massachusetts Institute of Technology
  - Lifschey, Samuel, 1917-1938, undated (Box-folder 61/4)
  - Lifschey, Samuel, 1939-1953 (Box-folder 61/5)
  - Ligne, Prince de see Belgium. Ambassador
  - Linch, Mabel E. see Philadelphia. Matinee Musical Club
  - Lincoln, Leland (Box-folder 61/6)
  - Linden (attorney) (Box-folder 61/7)
  - Lindholm, Carl B. (Box-folder 61/8)
  - Linn, Frances Burns see Santa Barbara (California) Public Library
  - Linsley, Ralph (Box-folder 61/9)
  - Lipa, Jaroslav see Czechoslovakia
  - Lipkin, Arthur Bennett (Box-folder 61/10)
  - Lit, Janice Reed (Mrs. David Ellis Lit) (Box-folder 61/11)
  - Litta, Paolo (Box-folder 61/12)
  - Little, Ramona (Box-folder 61/13)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, 1916-1925 (Box-folder 62/1)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, 1930-1933 (Box-folder 62/3)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 62/4)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 62/5)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 62/7)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 62/8)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 62/9)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, undated, Posted from Wilton, Connecticut. (Box-folder 62/10)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, undated, Posted from New York, 205 W. 94th St. (Box-folder 62/11)
  - Littlehales, Lillian, undated, Posted from miscellaneous addresses. (Box-folder 62/12)
  - Litwin, Leo (Box-folder 61/14)
  - "Ll" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 61/15)
  - Llewellyn, Edward B. (Box-folder 61/16)
  - Llewellyn, Louise (Box-folder 61/17)
  - Llobet, Miguel (Box-folder 61/18)
  - "Lo" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 61/19)
  - Locke, Arthur W. (Box-folder 61/20)
  - Lockwood, Normand (Box-folder 61/21)
  - Loeb, Arthur L. (Box-folder 61/22)
  - Loeffler, Charles Martin, 1918-1924 (Box-folder 61/23)
  - Loeffler, Charles Martin, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 61/24)
  - Loeffler, Charles Martin, 1928-1930 (Box-folder 61/25)
  - Loeffler, Charles Martin, 1932-1934 (Box-folder 61/26)
  - Loesser, Arthur (Box-folder 61/27)
  - Löwenbach, Jan (Box-folder 61/29)
  - Loewenguth Quartet (Box-folder 61/28)
  - London (Box-folder 61/30)
  - London. Royal Academy of Music (Box-folder 61/31)
  - London String Quartet (Box-folder 61/32)
  - Long, Kathleen (Box-folder 61/33)
  - Longy, Georges see also Boston Musical Association (Box-folder 61/34)
  - Longy Miquelle, Renée see Miquelle, Renée Longy
  - Longy School of Music (Box-folder 61/35)
  - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai (Box-folder 61/36)
  - Lorenz, Karl (Box-folder 61/37)
  - "Los" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 63/1)
  - Los Angeles Chamber Music Society (Box-folder 63/2)
  - Los Angeles. Hotels (Box-folder 63/3)
  - Los Angeles. Hotels. Hitchcock, Myrtle (Box-folder 63/4)
  - Los Angeles. Newspapers (Box-folder 63/5)
  - Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra (Box-folder 63/6)
  - Los Angeles Public Library see also Caldwell, Gladys (Box-folder 63/7)
  - Los Angeles. Miscellany (Box-folder 63/8)
  - Losey, Joseph (Box-folder 63/9)
  - Lothrop, Stanley see Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center
  - Louchheim, Walter, Mrs. (Box-folder 63/10)
  - Louisville, Kentucky (Box-folder 63/11)
  - "Lu" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 63/12)
  - Lualdi, Adriano (Box-folder 63/13)
  - Lubbock, Gurney and Mrs. (Box-folder 63/14)
  - Luce, Wendell H. (Box-folder 63/15)
  - Luchaire, Antonio Julien (Box-folder 63/16)
  - Lübbecke-Job, Emma and Lübbecke, Fried, 1927-1930 (Box-folder 63/17)
  - Lübbecke-Job, Emma and Lübbecke, Fried, 1931-1934 (Box-folder 63/18)
  - Lübbecke-Job, Emma and Lübbecke, Fried, undated (Box-folder 63/19)
  - Luening, Otto (Box-folder 63/20)
  - Lunt, Cornelia (Box-folder 63/21)
  - Lustgarten, Egon (Box-folder 63/22)
  - Lutkin, Peter C. (Box-folder 63/23)
  - Lyman, Ralph H. see Pomona College. Lyman, Ralph H.
  - Lyman, Stuart A. (Box-folder 63/24)
  - Lynde, Ethel Graham (Box-folder 63/25)
  - Lyon & Healy (Box-folder 63/26)
  - M. Steinert & Sons see Steinert, M. and sons
  - Maas, Gerald (Box-folder 64/2)
  - Maas, Marcel (Box-folder 64/3)
  - Maas, Robert see Pro Arte Quartet (Box-folder 64/4)
  - "MacA" and "McA" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 64/5)
  - McAfee, Mildred H. see Wellesley College. McAfee, Mildred H.
  - MacArden, Joy (Box-folder 64/7)
  - MacAusland, W. Russell (Box-folder 64/6)
  - MacColl, Hugh F. (Box-folder 64/8)
  - McCollin, Frances (Box-folder 64/9)
  - McCormack, John (Box-folder 64/10)
  - McCormick, Chauncey and Marion (Box-folder 64/11)
  - McCormick, Cyrus H. (Box-folder 64/12)
  - McCormick, Maud (Mrs. Alexander McCormick) (Box-folder 64/13)
  - McCoy, William J. (Box-folder 64/14)
  - McCulloch, Bertha (Box-folder 64/15)
  - "MacD" and "McD" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 64/16)
  - MacDonald-Hope, May see Hope, May MacDonald
  - McDonough, Mary-Catherine (Box-folder 64/17)
  - MacDougall, Hamilton C. see Wellesley College. MacDougall, Hamilton C.
  - MacDowell, Marian Nevins (MacDowell, Edward, Mrs.), 1917-1952 (Box-folder 64/18)
  - MacDowell, Marian Nevins (MacDowell, Edward, Mrs.), 1918-1932, undated (Box-folder 64/22)
  - MacDowell, Marian Nevins (MacDowell, Edward, Mrs.), undated (Box-folder 64/19)
  - MacDowell Association (Box-folder 64/20)
  - MacDowell Club of New York (Box-folder 64/21)
  - McDuffie, Jean Howard (Box-folder 64/23)
  - "MacE" and "McE" -- "MacK" and "McK" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 65/1)
  - McEwen, John B. see London. Royal Academy of Music
  - McGregor, Ruth (Box-folder 65/2)
  - Machabey, A. (Box-folder 65/3)
  - McIlvaine, Caroline (Box-folder 65/4)
  - McKay, George Frederick (Box-folder 65/5)
  - McKim, Leonora Jackson (Box-folder 65/6)
  - "MacL" and "McL" -- "MacW" and "McW" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 65/7)
  - MacLeish, Andrew and Mrs. (Box-folder 65/8)
  - MacLeish, Archibald see Library of Congress. MacLeish, Archibald
  - MacLellan, George W. (Box-folder 65/9)
  - MacLellan, Mabel (Box-folder 65/10)
  - McLennan, Grace Tytus (Box-folder 65/11)
  - McManus, George Stewart (Box-folder 65/12)
  - McManus, Lillian Whitney see Wellesley College. McManus, Lillian Whitney
  - Macmillan, Kerr Duncan (Box-folder 65/13)
  - McNeal, Edward K. (Box-folder 65/14)
  - McNeal, Katharine (Box-folder 65/15)
  - McQuesten, Robin and Fern (Box-folder 65/16)
  - McSweeney, Francis E. (Box-folder 65/17)
  - "Mad" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 65/18)
  - Maddison, Adela (Box-folder 65/19)
  - Maffioletti, Maria (Box-folder 65/20)
  - Magaloff, Nikita (Box-folder 65/21)
  - Magg, Fritz and Natasha (Box-folder 65/22)
  - Magnani, Fausto (Box-folder 65/23)
  - Magnard, Albéric (Mme.) (Box-folder 65/24)
  - Mahler, Alma see Werfel, Alma Mahler
  - Maier, Guy (Box-folder 65/25)
  - Mailamm see American Palestine Music Association
  - Maisel, Edward M. (Box-folder 65/26)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, undated, Presumably 1920-1932. (Box-folder 66/1)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1920-1924 (Box-folder 66/2)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 66/3)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1927 (Box-folder 66/4)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 66/5)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1930 (Box-folder 66/6)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1931 (Box-folder 66/7)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1932 (Box-folder 66/8)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1933 (Box-folder 66/9)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 66/10)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1936-1939 (Box-folder 66/11)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 66/12)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 66/13)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 66/14)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 66/15)
  - Malipiero, Gian Francesco and Anna, miscellany, undated (Box-folder 66/16)
  - Malipiero, Riccardo (Box-folder 65/27)
  - Malkin, Joseph (Box-folder 65/28)
  - "Man" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 65/29)
  - Mangeot, André (Box-folder 65/30)
  - Manhattan Storage and Warehouse Co. (Box-folder 65/31)
  - Mann, Flora (Box-folder 65/32)
  - Mann, Robert C. (Box-folder 65/33)
  - Mannes, David and Clara (Box-folder 65/34)
  - Mannes, Leopold Damrosch (Box-folder 65/35)
  - Mannes School of Music (Box-folder 65/36)
  - Manning, Helen Taft (Box-folder 65/37)
  - Manning, Warren H. (Box-folder 65/38)
  - Manship, Paul (Box-folder 65/39)
  - Manziarly, Marcelle de (Box-folder 65/40)
  - Maquarre, André (Box-folder 65/41)
  - "Mar" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 65/42)
  - Maragliano Mori, Rachele (Box-folder 65/43)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1927 (Box-folder 67/1)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1928 (Box-folder 67/2)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1929 (Box-folder 67/3)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1930 (Box-folder 67/4)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1931 (Box-folder 67/5)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1932 (Box-folder 67/6)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, undated, Probably pre-1933. (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1933 (Box-folder 67/8)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1934 (Box-folder 67/9)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1935 (Box-folder 67/10)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1936 (Box-folder 67/11)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1937 (Box-folder 67/12)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1938 (Box-folder 67/13)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1939 (Box-folder 67/14)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1940 (Box-folder 67/15)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 67/16)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 67/17)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 67/18)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 67/19)
  - Marchant, Luther and Marian, undated, Presumably not 1927-1932. (Box-folder 67/20)
  - Marchesi, Blanche (Box-folder 65/44)
  - Marcuse, Sibyl (Box-folder 65/45)
  - Margesson, Isabel (Box-folder 65/46)
  - "Mark" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 68/1)
  - Mark, Jeffrey (Box-folder 68/2)
  - Markevitch, Igor (Box-folder 68/3)
  - Marks, Jeannette (Box-folder 68/4)
  - Marlowe, Sylvia (Box-folder 68/5)
  - Marquand, John P., Mrs. see Hooker, Adelaide
  - Marshall, Harriet Gibbs (Box-folder 68/6)
  - Marsland, Myra (Box-folder 68/7)
  - Marteau, Henri (Box-folder 68/8)
  - Martí, Samuel (Box-folder 68/9)
  - Martin, Florence (Box-folder 68/10)
  - Martin, Martha, 1922-1939 (Box-folder 68/11)
  - Martin, Martha, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 68/12)
  - Martin, Martha, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 68/13)
  - Martin, Martha, undated (Box-folder 68/14)
  - Martinů, Bohuslav, 1927-1930 (Box-folder 68/15)
  - Martinů, Bohuslav, 1931-1941, undated (Box-folder 68/16)
  - Marum, Ludwig (Box-folder 68/17)
  - Marx, Benjamin L. see Honolulu Art Society
  - "Mas" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 68/18)
  - Mason, Daniel Gregory and Mrs., 1914-1919 (Box-folder 68/19)
  - Mason, Daniel Gregory and Mrs., 1920-1929 (Box-folder 68/20)
  - Mason, Daniel Gregory and Mrs., 1930-1938 (Box-folder 68/21)
  - Mason, Henry Lowell (Box-folder 68/22)
  - Masaryk, Jan (secretarial) (Box-folder 68/23)
  - Massachusetts (state officials and documents) (Box-folder 68/24)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital (Box-folder 68/25)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box-folder 68/26)
  - Massey, Alice Vincent (Box-folder 68/27)
  - Matinée Musical Club see Philadelphia. Matinée Musical Club
  - Matthews, Charles H. (Box-folder 68/28)
  - Matthison, Edith Wynne see Kennedy, Charles Rann and Edith Wynne
  - Matzenauer, Margarete (Box-folder 68/29)
  - Maude, Cecily (Box-folder 68/30)
  - Mauk, Marielies (Box-folder 68/31)
  - Mauke, Alex (Box-folder 68/32)
  - Mayer, Daniel (Box-folder 68/33)
  - Mayer, Dorothy Moulton see Mayer, Robert and Dorothy
  - Mayer, F. C. (Box-folder 68/34)
  - Mayer, Robert and Dorothy (Box-folder 68/35)
  - Mayes, Samuel and Mrs. (Box-folder 68/36)
  - Maynard's Secretarial Bureau (Box-folder 68/37)
  - Mazzeo, Rosario and Mildred (Box-folder 68/38)
  - "Me" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 69/1)
  - Meader, George Farnham (Box-folder 69/2)
  - Meaker, Stanleigh R. (Box-folder 69/3)
  - Mears, Eliot G. see Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys
  - Meeker, Grace (Box-folder 69/4)
  - Meester, A. Roland Holot de (Box-folder 69/5)
  - Melchers, Gari (Box-folder 69/6)
  - Mencken, Henry L. (Box-folder 69/7)
  - Mengelberg, Rudolf (Box-folder 69/8)
  - Mengelberg, Willem (Box-folder 69/9)
  - Merritt, A. Tillman see Harvard University. Merritt, A. Tillman
  - Meremblum, Peter (Box-folder 69/10)
  - Merovich, Alexander (Box-folder 69/11)
  - Merrill, Margaret Bell (Box-folder 69/12)
  - Mertens, Fernand (Box-folder 69/13)
  - Mesirow-Minchin, Nina (Box-folder 69/14)
  - Metcalf, Jesse H. and Mrs. (Box-folder 69/15)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York, N.Y.) see New York. Metropolitan Museum of Art
  - Metropolitan Musical Bureau (Box-folder 69/16)
  - Mexico (Box-folder 69/17)
  - Meyer, Agnes (Mrs. Eugene Meyer) (Box-folder 69/18)
  - Meyer, Andreas (Box-folder 69/19)
  - Meyer, Annie Nathan (Mrs. Alfred Meyer) (Box-folder 69/20)
  - Meyer, Dorothy see National Broadcasting Company. Meyer, Dorothy
  - Meyer, H.H.B. (Box-folder 69/21)
  - Meyer, Sylvia (Box-folder 69/22)
  - Meyers, Emerson (Box-folder 69/23)
  - Meyers, Persis Clare (Box-folder 69/24)
  - "Mi" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 69/25)
  - Miami University, Oxford, Ohio (Box-folder 69/26)
  - Michel, Dr. see Frankfurt am Main
  - Mid-West Music Foundation (Box-folder 69/27)
  - Migot, Georges (Box-folder 69/28)
  - Mikota, Jan (Box-folder 69/29)
  - Milan (Box-folder 69/30)
  - Milan. Gruppo Universitario di Cultura Musicale (Box-folder 69/31)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, undated, Probably pre-1933. (Box-folder 69/32)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, 1927-1933 (Box-folder 69/33)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 69/34)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 69/35)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, 1943-1947 (Box-folder 69/36)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 69/37)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, undated, Posted from 10 Boulevard de Clichy. (Box-folder 69/38)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, undated, European posts (other than Rue de Clichy). (Box-folder 69/39)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, undated, Posted from Mills College. (Box-folder 69/40)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, undated, American posts, other than Mills College. (Box-folder 69/41)
  - Milhaud, Darius and Madeline, undated, No definite place. (Box-folder 69/42)
  - "Mill" miscellaneous see also "M" miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 70/1)
  - Miller, Charles (Box-folder 70/2)